# **Unyime Emmanuel**

Lagos, Lagos State, Nigeria

unyimeemmanuel012@gmail.com

07066261517

linkedin.com/in/unyime-emmanuel-31a2021b3

## Summary

I'm a prolific web developer with a passion for data structures and beating former "best yets". I create responsive and interactive websites that are SEO-friendly, thus decreasing overall access issues by 90% and increasing user experience by 60%. Constantly receive high user experience scores for all web development projects like the ones done on frontendentor. Passionate about building web apps with implementation of object-oriented and functional programming.

## **Experience**

#### Frontend Web Developer

Garmspot

Jun 2022 - Present (7 months +)

#### **Frontend Developer**

Yefepere

Dec 2020 - Present (2 years 1 month +)

#### Web Development Project Manager

2121

Nov 2022 - Dec 2022 (2 months)

A website created for a fashion exhibition inspired by sci-fi that aims to view alternate realities through fashion.



#### Web Developer

Haqqman

Apr 2022 - Sep 2022 (6 months)

#### **Frontend Web Developer**

1938&Co

Mar 2020 - Jun 2020 (4 months)

#### **Education**



#### University of Uyo

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Chemical Technology/Technician 2019 - 2023

#### **Licenses & Certifications**



# (A) Responsive Web Design - freeCodeCamp

# **Skills**

TypeScript • Next.js • Tailwind CSS • WordPress Design • Redux.js • MongoDB • Scrum • Git • Node.js • PHP